<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CytoData 2018</title>
    <link>http://cytodata.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CytoData 2018</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 15:31:58 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cytodata.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Attend</title>
      <link>http://cytodata.org/why-attend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 15:31:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cytodata.org/why-attend/</guid>
      <description>The world of image-based profiling harvests the rich information available in high throughput image assays. Over the last years, this research field changed from proof-of-principle to field that lead to many biological discoveries! Since our first hackathon in 2016, the world of image based profiling became even more exciting! We formed the CytoData Society with the focus on image based profiling to share and extend our enthusiasm and knowledge. In 2018, we again invite everyone from the novel student to the leading experts in this field to Boston.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>http://cytodata.org/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 15:33:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cytodata.org/schedule/</guid>
      <description>         Fri 9/21 Full day Symposium Get in touch with leading researchers in the field of image-based profiling from industry and academia   Mon 9/24 CytoData Hackathon - day 1 Community-driven project, more t.b.a.   Tue 9/25 CytoData Hackathon - day 2 Profiling challenge - we will hack in teams and compete in a CytoData challenge!    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logistics</title>
      <link>http://cytodata.org/logistics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 15:54:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cytodata.org/logistics/</guid>
      <description>Funding The Each participant should plan to finance their own travel and lodging (exception: some support can be provided for attendees from under-represented groups; please contact us). Please note that space is limited in order to maintain high levels of engagement.
Transportation The closest airport is Boston Logan Airport (BOS). The Broad Institute is accessible by the MBTA red line at the Kendall/MIT stop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organizers</title>
      <link>http://cytodata.org/organizers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 15:55:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cytodata.org/organizers/</guid>
      <description>The CytoData society (CytoDS) is an international society that builds and maintains an active community around image-based profiling of biological phenotypes induced by genetic, chemical or other perturbations of biological systems. This field is still in its infancy, and its adoption has been slow, primarily due to the data analysis challenges posed, the large imaging experiments required, and the lack of ground-truth data sets where relationships among images are known. Our goal is therefore to bring image-based profiling into the mainstream by organizing the community working on this technology.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>